fuzu.com 2016-10-17

# Fuzu Privacy policy - Plan career, learn skills and find latest jobs in Kenya

## FUZU Privacy Policy for products and services

Effective date 7th of September 2015

### WE CARE ABOUT YOUR PRIVACY

FUZU Ltd (corporate ID 2546225-2), including its affiliates, is committed to respecting your privacy and to complying with applicable data protection and privacy laws. This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how we collect and use personal data where FUZU is the data controller or where we refer to the applicability of this Policy. “Personal data” means all information relating to you or another identifiable individual, such as another user or employer.

We will give you additional privacy information in notices you may see while using our services. If there is a difference between such notices and this Policy, the notices should be considered first.

Our services may contain links to other companies’ websites and services that have privacy policies of their own. FUZU is not responsible for the privacy practices of others and we recommend you read their privacy notices.

 **If you do not agree with this Policy, do not use our products and services or provide FUZU with your personal data.**

### What information do we collect?

#### Your profile and activities:

We collect the content and other types of personal data you provide when you use our Services. This includes personal data provided while registering to FUZU, building of your personal profile, sharing of updates, applying for jobs, taking courses and different types of tests and communicating with other users. This can include information in or about the content you provide, such as the location or the date the data was created. We also collect information about how you use our Services, such as the types of content you view or engage with or the frequency and duration of your activities. We may, in accordance with applicable law, record your communication with our customer care or with other such contact points.

#### Your connections:

We collect information about the other users and groups you are connected to and how you interact with them, such as the people you communicate with the most or the groups you like to share updates with.

#### Your payment information:

When you purchase FUZU paid-for Premium features we collect information about the purchase or transaction. This includes your payment information, such as your credit or debit card number and other card information, and other account and authentication information, as well as billing and contact details, such as your phone number.

#### Your devices:

To continuously improve the Service we collect information about the computers, phones, or other devices where you install or access our Services, depending on the permissions you’ve granted.

### Why Do We Process Personal Data?

FUZU may process your personal data for the following purposes. One or more purposes may apply simultaneously.

  *  **Providing products and services**

We may use your personal data to provide you with our services and content, to process your requests or as otherwise may be necessary to perform the contract between you and FUZU, to ensure the functionality and security of our services and content, to identify you as well as to prevent and investigate fraud and other misuses.

  *  **Accounts** requires an account to help you manage your personal information, content and preferences.
  *  **Developing and managing services and content**

We may use your personal data to develop and manage our services, software, content, customer care, sales and marketing. We may combine personal data collected in connection with your use of a particular FUZU service or content with other personal data we may have about you, unless such personal data was collected for a different purpose.

  *  **Communicating with you**

We may use your personal data to communicate with you, for example to inform you that our services have changed or to send you critical alerts and other such notices relating to our products and/or services and to contact you for customer care related purposes.

  *  **Marketing, advertising and making recommendations**

We may contact you to inform you of new services, content or promotions we may offer and to conduct market research when we have your consent or it is otherwise allowed. We may use your personal data to personalise our offering and to provide you with more relevant ads and services, for example, recommend jobs or training content. This may include displaying FUZU and third party content.

  *  **Promote safety and security**

We use the information we have to help verify accounts and activity, and to promote safety and security on and off of our Services, such as by investigating suspicious activity or violations of our terms or policies. We work hard to protect your account using specialists, automated systems, and advanced technology such as encryption.

### Do we share personal data?

Users use our services for their own personal development or for interacting with other Users. Your personal data is shared in the following ways:

 **Users you share and communicate with:**

FUZU service includes various forms of communication and sharing with other users. Different scenarios include:

 **Applying for a job:**

When you apply for a job you consent to sharing of your personal data, including application data and test results, with the employer.

 **Headhunting:**

You may also decide to share your profile with the employers for headhunting purposes, who can then access your personal data limited to your user profile and test results, such as personality profile used for applying for jobs. In headhunting mode your contact information is not shared, but will require separate consent from you. Visibility to headhunters can be managed under user settings.

 **Direct communication with other users:**

Your private communication with other users, both individuals and employers, remains private to you and the other party.

 **Career Hub:**

All activities conducted in Career Hub, including taking courses and tests are by default private and cannot be seen by other users. You may choose to take a skill test to verify and accredit a skill, which can then be published on your profile or shared proactively with other users.

 **User updates**

Updates and postings on FUZU are by default visible to all FUZU Users, unless targeted for a specific group of users.

Please consider carefully before disclosing any personal data or other information that might be accessible to other users.

### Sharing within FUZU companies or third parties:

We may share your personal data with FUZU companies or third parties who process personal data for FUZU for the purposes described in this Policy. This may include for example billing through your network service provider or otherwise, delivery of your purchases, providing services including customer service, managing and analysing consumer data, credit checks, conducting research and managing marketing and other such campaigns. When you purchase a FUZU service from us with a network service provider plan, we may need to exchange information with your network service provider to provide you with such service.

Sharing of information with third parties includes entities providing advertising, measurement and analytics services.

We want our advertising to be as relevant and interesting as the other information you find on our Services. With this in mind, we use all of the information we have about you to show you relevant ads. We do not share information that personally identifies you (personally identifiable information is information like name or email address that can by itself be used to contact you or identifies who you are) with advertising, measurement or analytics partners unless you give us permission. We may provide these partners with information about the reach and effectiveness of their advertising without providing information that personally identifies you, or if we have aggregated the information so that it does not personally identify you. For example, we may tell an advertiser how its ads performed, or how many people viewed their ads or installed an app after seeing an ad, or provide non-personally identifying demographic information (such as 18 year old female, in Nairobi, who likes software engineering) to these partners to help them understand their audience or customers, but only after the advertiser has agreed to abide by our advertiser guidelines.

These authorised third parties are not permitted to use your personal data for any other purposes. We require them to act consistently with this Policy and to use appropriate security measures to protect your personal data.

  *  **International transfers of personal data**

Our products and services may be provided using resources and servers located in various countries around the world. Therefore your personal data may be transferred across international borders outside the country where you use our services, including to countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA) that do not have laws providing specific protection for personal data or that have different legal rules on data protection, for example, the United States of America. In such cases we ensure that there is a legal basis for such a transfer and that adequate protection for your personal data is provided as required by applicable law, for example, by using standard agreements approved by relevant authorities (where necessary) and by requiring the use of other appropriate technical and organisational information security measures.

  *  **Mandatory disclosures**

We may be obligated by mandatory law to disclose your personal data to certain authorities or other third parties, for example, to law enforcement agencies in the countries where we or third parties acting on our behalf operate. We may also disclose and otherwise process your personal data in accordance with applicable law to defend FUZU’s legitimate interests, for example, in civil or criminal legal proceedings.

 **New owner: p If the ownership or control of all or part of our Services or their assets changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner.**

### How do we enforce privacy and data quality?

#### How do we address the privacy of children?

FUZU Services have been designed for adult users of eighteen (18) years and above. FUZU does not knowingly collect information of children without the consent of their parents or guardians.

#### How do we address data quality?

 **We take reasonable steps to keep the personal data we possess accurate and to delete incorrect or unnecessary personal data.**

We encourage you to access your personal data through your account from time to time to ensure that it is up to date.

#### What steps are taken to safeguard personal data?

Privacy and security are key considerations in the creation and delivery of our Services. We take appropriate steps to address online security, physical security, risk of data loss and other such risks taking into consideration the risk represented by the processing and the nature of the data being protected. Also, we limit access to our data bases containing personal data to authorised persons having a justified need to access such information.

### How do we use cookies and web beacons?

FUZU uses cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies to operate and improve our websites and offering. We also use cookies for personalisation and to display ads. Some FUZU websites use third party advertising technologies, such as DoubleClick, to serve ads.

Our domains may include third party elements that set cookies on behalf of a third party, for example relating to third party social network.

### What are your rights?

You have a right to know what personal data we hold about you. You have a right to have incomplete, incorrect, unnecessary or outdated personal data deleted or updated.

You may exercise your rights by contacting us or by managing your account and choices through available profile management tools on your device and our services. In some cases, especially if you wish us to delete or stop processing your personal data, this may also mean that we may not be able to continue to provide the services to you.

### Who is the controller of your personal data?

FUZU Ltd (corporate ID 2546225-2), Siltavuorenpenger 7, 00170 Helsinki, Finland is the controller of your personal data.

In addition, the FUZU affiliate providing the product or service may be a controller of your personal data. You may find the identity of the controller and its contact details by reviewing the terms and conditions of such a product or service or by using contact information provided in the applicable FUZU websites.

In matters pertaining to FUZU’s privacy practices you may also contact us at the address above or our email support@fuzu.com

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

FUZU may from time to time change this Policy or change, modify or withdraw access to this site at any time with or without notice. However, if this Policy is changed in a material, adverse way, FUZU will post a notice advising of such change at the beginning of this Policy and on this site’s home page for 30 days. We recommend that you re-visit this Policy from time to time to learn of any such changes to this Policy.
